<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>umcconnell</title>
    <subtitle>Just my personal website</subtitle>
    <link href="https://umcconnell.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
    <link href="https://umcconnell.github.io" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <author>
        <name>umcconnell</name>
    </author>
    
    <updated>2021-03-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
    
    <id>https://umcconnell.github.io/</id>
        <entry>
            <title>Hello Internet</title>
            <link href="https://umcconnell.github.io/posts/2021-03-11-hello-internet/"/>
            <updated>2021-03-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
            <id>https://umcconnell.github.io/posts/2021-03-11-hello-internet/</id>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[
                <p>Hi!</p>
<p>This is the first post on my new blog, and I’m really excited. I hope to write
more in the coming weeks and months, especially about technical and
software-related topics. My goal is to write about current software side
projects and things I’ve learned, all in the spirit of
“Stay curious, keep learning”. Depending on how that works out, I’ll adapt if
needed.</p>
<h2 id="outlook">Outlook</h2>
<p>A few topics I’d like to cover soon are AI, Rust and how I set up this blog, to
give some ideas in case you would like to do the same. In the meantime, as this
blog is entirely open source, I invite you to check out the
<a href="https://github.com/umcconnell/umcconnell.github.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">source code<svg class="icon icon--link-external" role="img" aria-hidden="true" width="24" height="24">
        <use xlink:href="#icon-link-external"></use>
        </svg></a> on Github,
fork it, make it your own, or whatever you want.</p>
<h2 id="why">Why?!?</h2>
<p>I hope to learn something useful from this experience and gain some more
experience building websites. Writing down ideas and summarizing problems is a
good exercise, all while improving writing skills. A blog also let’s me document
findings and ideas for later use or for someone else to be inspired.</p>
<p>And maybe I can even help solve a problem on the way or motivate to learn
something new!</p>
<p>Feel free to comment on any post, give feedback, suggest improvements, correct
me or whatever else you think is appropriate.</p>
<p>Cheers!</p>
<p>- Ulysse</p>

            ]]></content>
        </entry></feed>